<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>General on Kostas Kougioumoutzis</title>
    <link>https://www.kkougiou.com/categories/general/</link>
    <description>Recent content in General on Kostas Kougioumoutzis</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2020 Kostas Kougioumoutzis</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.kkougiou.com/categories/general/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Second year of SoBEx</title>
      <link>https://www.kkougiou.com/post/2021-01-25-second-year-of-sobex/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Jan 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kkougiou.com/post/2021-01-25-second-year-of-sobex/</guid>
      <description>body {text-align: justify}OverviewThe second year of SoBEx has been hard, since due to covid-19 restrictions our team was not able to work properly or conduct field research for all the species we study.
What has been doneSo far we have conducted molecular/genetic analyses for most of the studied animal and plant taxa. We have also run several macroecological analyses so as to estimate the effects of climate change on these Critically Endangered species, as well as to estimate the percent overlap of these species’ distribution range with the NATURA 2000 protected areas network (PAs - gap analysis).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>First year of SoBEx</title>
      <link>https://www.kkougiou.com/post/sobex-post/first-year-of-sobex/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kkougiou.com/post/sobex-post/first-year-of-sobex/</guid>
      <description>body {text-align: justify}OverviewDuring the past year, the SoBEx team, together with Yannis Alexiou, Gabriela Kelaidi and Chrysa Papadaki, three post-graduate students in UAMECO lab has been conducting field work in several Aegean islands (Figure 1), mainland Greek mountains (Figure 2) and lakes, so as to collect population and environmental data for the Critically Endangered Greek endemic animal and plant species (according to the IUCN).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Short-term vacancy</title>
      <link>https://www.kkougiou.com/post/short-term-vacancy/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 29 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kkougiou.com/post/short-term-vacancy/</guid>
      <description>Job opening In our project entitled Species on the brink of extinction funded by the Hellenic Foundation for Research and Innovation (HFRI) and the General Secretariat for Research and Technology (GSRT) under grant agreement No 2418, we are offering one (1) short-term post-graduate position.
Requirements If you are enthusiastic about working in the field, collecting plant samples and have (some) experience in and molecular/genetic techniques (especially in ISSRs), then you should probably consider to apply for this position.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Join the lab</title>
      <link>https://www.kkougiou.com/post/second-post/join-the-lab/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 10 Feb 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kkougiou.com/post/second-post/join-the-lab/</guid>
      <description>Job opening In our project entitled Species on the brink of extinction funded by the Hellenic Foundation for Research and Innovation (HFRI) and the General Secretariat for Research and Technology (GSRT) under grant agreement No 2418, we are offering three (3) short-term post-graduate positions.
Requirements If you are enthusiastic about working in the field, collecting plant and animal samples and have (some) experience in spatial analysis, species distribution modelling and molecular/genetic techniques, then you should probably consider to apply for one of these positions.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>A small intro</title>
      <link>https://www.kkougiou.com/post/first-post/how-i-am-and-what-s-this-blog-going-to-be-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jan 2019 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.kkougiou.com/post/first-post/how-i-am-and-what-s-this-blog-going-to-be-about/</guid>
      <description>In this blog I am going to share my thoughts on some papers that I find interesting (and hopefully you too), several how-to’s regarding several types of analysis in R and maybe photos from all my field-trips!
But first of all, let me introduce myself1:
General InfoI was born and raised in Athens (Figure 1) in the early, glorious 80s, but I come from the land of plenty.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>